CONNOR RHODES

11600 Minda Cir Austin, Texas 78758 https://connor.engineer
linkedin.com/in/0xConnorRhodes

connor@rhodes.contact (405) 990 - 1104

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Solutions engineer with 5+ years of industry experience. Strong technical background including network engineering, Linux, scripting and automation, and cloud technologies. In-depth familiarity with Verkada's product lines, architecture and backend tooling. Experience working with sales managers and account executives to shape territories and improve the execution of the sales process.

TECHNICAL CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco CCNA
Comptia Network+
Comptia IT Operations Specialist

Comptia Cloud Essentials+
Brainbench Security Industry Knowledge
Comptia A+

WORK EXPERIENCE

Verkada Inc.

Jun 2021 – Present

SOLUTIONS ENGINEER

- **Designed Custom Solutions to Close Deals:** Worked with account executives to qualify and prioritize customer requests. Designed custom software and low voltage solutions to meet customer needs. Worked with the product team to develop new features to win deals. Solutions included custom low-voltage integrations, mustering, and alarm system auto re-arm.
- **Developed Internal Documentation and Tools:** Wrote and gave internal technical training on engineering topics including SAML, SCIM, and Verkada's internal support tools. Designed and built internal network testing hardware and software to assist with the deployment of key deals.
- Built Relationships with Manufacturers and Partner Companies: Onboarded strategic partners across Alabama and Georgia leading to more closed deals and a faster deal cycle. Built relationships and developed integrations with manufacturers of complementary products. Integrations included perimeter monitoring, employee temperature checks, and door control integration into third-party software.

Servsys Corporation

Jan 2020 – June 2020

SALES ENGINEER

- Opportunity Discovery and Qualification: Assessed the design, performance, and security of prospects' networks. Spoke with prospects about their current IT capabilities and challenges. Provided technical oversight to proof-of-value presentations given to prospects.
- Systems Engineering and Automation: Designed and implemented marketing automation server using Linux and cloud technologies. This server enabled marketing and prospecting communication to be tracked and automated.

University of Dallas

Aug 2012 – May 2016

TECHNICAL ASSISTANT

- **Project Management and Systems Design:** Designed, implemented, and administered an automation server to track and report changes in distance learning regulation across all 50 states.
- Strong Written and Verbal Communication Skills: Evaluated various potential software vendors. Collaborated with the Director to communicate with vendors. Developed in-house documentation of vendor tools including the Brightspace API and Qualtrics experience management software.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy. University of Dallas (Irving, TX)

- GPA in Major (18 courses): 4.0/4.0, Overall GPA: 3.9/4.0
- Summa Cum Laude

Diploma in Computer Information Systems. Canadian Valley Technology Center (El Reno, OK)

- GPA in Program: 4.0/4.0
- National Technical Honors Society